[Music]
simple comprehensive
fantastic
affordable
assurance
[Music]
when i first learned about the product i
was pleasantly surprised to know it is
quite simple to understand
fwds recover first is a fantastic plan
the streamlined definitions and reduced
complexities of fwd recovery first stood
up to me the most
not just for its easy to digest
information but also its extensive
coverage so energies this is an
insurance plan that exudes inclusivity
and simplicity
something that many singaporeans are
increasingly looking for in their
planning process
fwd recover first provides excellent and
comprehensive critical unions coverage
with medical advancement new illnesses
are discovered every day and it's hard
for any predefined list of critical
illnesses to cover emerging illnesses
the future protect benefit prejudice
this gap as it provides a payout by the
impact an illness has on one's body
fwd recover first is a product with easy
to understand features and this is
important because no matter how good the
product's features are the clients have
to understand them in terms of the
course
it's very competitive
as a financial advisor representative
who has access to multiverse providers
products
i am able to make the comparisons and
fwd recover first stand up from the pack
in terms of costing and positioning
what's also good is that the courage is
not limited to what is known today
it also provide courage for what may
potentially strike unexpectedly in the
future
will be simplicity that fits right in
fwd recover first is model on simplicity
therefore it's no surprise that fwd
strives to make securing the critical
illness protection you need as simple as
possible from application to
underwriting no redundant questions
asked even as modern medicine advances
with the advance of new technologies and
innovation there will always be a day
where a new disease or illness is
discovered just like kovit 19. when that
happens you can rest assured knowing
that your plan comes with future protect
benefit that shields you against any
future uncertainties or unwanted
surprises
i have this client with congenital heart
issue born with a hole in the heart i
met him last year for financial planning
and he was concerned about his critical
illness coverage
health-wise he is in his 20s young and
healthy having said that the client
faced rejection and exclusions from
other insurers however fwd studied this
case and after careful consideration of
the application with declarations and
reports provided the client was able to
get 100 coverage from fwd recover first
the whole process really illustrated to
me how fwd is an insurer that truly
cares and changes the way people feel
about insurance
[Music]
yes it's quite good for those who are
concerned about their health so most
people do not wake up in the morning
thinking hmm what should i be buying for
critical illness insurance for those who
are serious about reviewing their
coverage i shared with them recover
first and how he stacks up against the
other plans the feedback has been
positive with most saying that the price
point is competitive and features are
also comprehensive
[Music]
fwd recover first provides coverage for
every stage of critical illnesses early
intermediate and late stage illnesses
and one of my favorite features would be
the reset benefit let me explain upon
diagnosis of a critical illness fwd will
pay the insured amount to the client and
after a waiting period of 12 months
the policy will reset or revert back to
provide 100 coverage to the client
do note that once the first payout is
given to the client all future premiums
are automatically waived off
there is no such thing as a
one-size-fits-all insurance policy
ask insightful questions about other
options to find out how they compare to
the ones recommended to you
ask yourself am i being told only about
the benefits or do i also know the
potential drawbacks
the pandemic has taught us that it is
imperative to have robust medical and
investment plans today you discovered 19
tomorrow it could be something else we
cannot control life's uncertainties but
we can definitely plan for it to
substantiate cancer stroke or heart
attack may or may not happen but in the
event it happens
fwd recovers can provide that much
needed financial cushioning
[Music]
you